(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Shall we start?
Okay.
Okay sir, Vanakkam sir.
How do you feel?
You have won an award.
Madam, my sugar level is 8.8. Average
is 5.8. Before breakfast, it was 120.
After that, it was only 130.
Because of your treatment, my sugar level has
come up to this level.
I would like to convey my heartfelt wishes
to you.
Did you expect this day to come in
your life?
Of course not.
I have never met a girl like her.
We have come all the way from Coimbatore
for this.
I would like to convey my heartfelt wishes
to your team.
We are going to split your journey into
two parts.
Before joining My Health School, you would have
faced many problems.
Do you have any changes after joining My
Health School?
In our family, we all eat bar food.
Because of Sudarshan sir's diet, we have stopped
eating idli and dosa.
We have started eating ragi.
Our body weight has reduced.
We are all healthy in our family.
I would like to convey my heartfelt wishes
to your team.
to my team.
Your health coach has supported you.
How did your parents support you?
My health coach is Sumathi.
She has regularly checked my health condition.
She has checked my blood sugar level and
my diet.
She has checked everything.
I would like to convey my heartfelt wishes
to her.
Many people want to join your team.
But due to some reasons, they cannot join.
They may have a trust issue or fear.
What advice do you want to give to
such people?
Actually, many people don't know about this.
They think that they will be given some
medicine if they go.
If we say that we don't have any
medicine, people like us will join for sure.
7-8 people like me will join for
sure.
Many people have joined.
What advice would you give to them?
Follow farmers.
If you follow that, you will be 100
% cured.
Super, super sir.
We can understand that you are following everything.
We can understand that there are many changes
in your rehearsal journey.
If you want to say a word to
sir, you can look at this camera and
say.
Actually, not everyone will get a chance.
Sir will say, this is your chance.
If you come, come.
If you don't come, go.
This gift was given by God to us
by Sudha sir and Dr. Prabhakar.
I sincerely thank God.
Thank you sir, thank you.
Enjoy the event.
Thank you.